

Prague, Czech Republic



lukas.bunat@gmail.com



+420 731 277 533



www.lukasbunat.eu



bunatl



lukasbunat



Software & Full-Stack Developer and Data Engineer

I am a tech enthusiastic born in Prague, Czech Republic. I have had studied at many different universities all over the world and I take great pride in my international experience. It showed and taught me different approaches on how to deal with problems. I always do my best to achieve my dreams and goals. Over time I found out that I can easily learn new things and make a good decision. I believe it is also thanks to my vast knowledge.

I started as a software developer with languages such as C, C++ and JAVA where the main objectives were speed, efficiency and design patterns. Later, I have found my passion for Full-Stack and since then I put my focus into web development. In the future, I want to learn blockchain technologies. As I do see huge potential in these technologies. However, I don't just code, I have a wide range of analytics and systematic skills that helps me finding clever solutions for improving/creating optimal programs.



Technical Skills

Programming language
Collaboration
Theoretical informatics
Computer architecture

Other

C/C++, JAVA SE/EE, JS, node.js, react.js, bash, SQL, No-SQL

GIT, Docker & JIRA, Trello, Slack

Calculus, Linear Algebra & Algorithms, Efficiency, Code optimization

Data and number representation, OS/memory/cache/FS management, multitasking

Business Intelligence, UML, Testing

Data analysis, Logical thinking, Critical analytical thinking



Soft Skills



New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic about learn new things and technologies



Quick decisiveness, good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time mangment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Certificates



CISCO Academy

CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk AutoCAD (2014) Inventor (2014)



KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme

Work Experiences

Freelancer

09/2019 - Present

- Websites and small web application
- ➤ JS, node.js, react
- Wordpress

Network Infrastructure Specialist 05/2018–05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s., Prague, Czech Republic

- Software development of O2TV platform and its internal applications
- C, Java EE, JS, HTML, CSS, GitHub

Internships

Big Data Architect Trainee 10/2017–12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University, Madrid, Spain

- Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy
- PySpark, Jupyter, Hadoop

Network Engineer Trainee 03/2017–06/2017

Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea

- ➤ Network Simulations on COOJA Simulator
- Wireshark, COOJA

I had been working as a tutor at international student club at Czech Technical University since 2014 till 2019 when I left the university. Previously, I had worked as a financial advisor in OVB during 2011 to 2013 and as a teacher at Korean high school while I was studying in South Korea. Currently, I am tutoring some university IT courses.



Education

University, Year(s) of Study		Field of study, Faculty	Location
Story Export	University of Economics	Information systems and technologies	Prague,
PRAZE	2019 - Present	Faculty of informatics and statistics	Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague, Czech Republic
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	
ISIS	University of Finance and Administration	Applied Informatics, Graduate, Bc.	Prague,
	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	▼ Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague,
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	Czech Republic
THE THE PARTY OF T	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	Daegu, South Korea
	2017	College of IT Engineering	
A CONTROL OF THE CONT	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai, India
	2016	Department of Computer Science	
THE COCCULATION OF THE PARTY OF	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	P Delft, Netherlands
	2016	The ATHENS Programme	
	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth, United Kingdom
	2012		